kiwicollection.com 2016-06-24

# Privacy | Kiwi Collection

As you would expect from all the premier properties showcased in our publications and on our website, Kiwi Collection Inc. respects your privacy and will take all reasonable measures to protect it. We will not sell, share, rent, or otherwise provide any personal information you have given us, to any third party without your permission. 

Kiwi Collection Inc. will not collect any personal information about individuals except when specifically and knowingly provided by such individuals. Our servers collect data each time a user navigates our site. This information is anonymous in nature and includes such information as the number, frequency and duration of each visit, as well as details about click-throughs to our Property Member sites and other third party sites. We will share this non-personal, aggregate, or summary information with partners or other third parties, but Kiwi Collection Inc. will not sell or share any information at the individual level. 

All personal information you do give us will be used exclusively by Kiwi Collection Inc. to communicate directly with you, or with the hotels displayed on our website, for the purpose of arranging your hotel bookings or answering questions about a booking. Any information you give us will not be used in ways to which you have not consented. At any time you may ask us to discontinue use of the information you have provided, and request that we refrain from sending any further communications to you via that information, by simply sending us a request at [info@kiwicollection.com](mailto:info@kiwicollection.com). Kiwi Collection Inc. commits to accept and abide by such a request immediately.

We do reserve the right to change this policy as we expand or alter our services. Accordingly we recommend that you check from time to time in order to understand how we treat your personal information. Your use of this website and its services constitute your agreement to the terms of our privacy policy. If we change those policies, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what personal information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it. Your continued use of this website and its services constitute your agreement to any such changes.

If you have any questions or concerns feel free to email us. 

## Browsing and the use of cookies, Web beacons and other tracking technologies

Kiwi Collection uses cookie technology as part of the Website's statistical reporting and for other purposes related to making the collection available to you. A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a website that is saved on your hard disk by your computer's browser. It holds information a website may need to personalize your experience (such as, rotating images on the home page of the Website). We also utilize cookies to identify if you are logged into your Account.

If you prefer, you can configure your browser to reject all cookies, or to notify you when a cookie is set. Each browser is different, so check the 'Help' menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie and privacy preferences. However, if you reject cookies, your use of the Website will be materially impaired or may altogether preclude your use of the Website.

A Web beacon is an electronic image, also called a single-pixel or clear GIF, placed in the code of a webpage or in emails. The Website uses Web beacons to track traffic patterns of users as they navigate from one page to another. This information lets us tune and improve our users' browsing experience. As with cookies, the information that Web beacons collect is aggregated, anonymous 'click stream' data, and is not associated with you as an individual.

We may use third parties to operate on our behalf to help manage and optimize our Internet business and communications. Through the use of cookies and Action Tags (commonly referred to as Web beacons or GIF tags - e.g., Atlas cookies and Action Tags, Omniture tags, and Doubleclick Web beacons), which are inserted in various places within the Website, such third party companies may collect anonymous information about your visits to the Website and your interaction with our ads and content. For instance, they may keep track of how many of our ads you had seen before visiting the Website. These third party companies may share such anonymous information about your visits to this and other websites with us. From time to time, we may also share anonymous information with such third party companies in an aggregate form, for purposes of analysis and improvement of the Website. If you would like more information about the use of third-party cookies and tags, or the process of opting out of such cookies or tags, please go to  [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/), <http://www.omniture.com/en/privacy/2o7> and <http://www.omniture.com/privacy/product#optout>. Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the Ads Settings.

We also use Web beacons through a third party website analytics provider (Google Analytics or other provider), as well as standard Web server log files, to help us count visitors and evaluate the Website's technical capacity. We also utilize Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. This information tells us how many people visit the Website, and helps us decide how to arrange pages in the most user-friendly way. This also helps us keep the Website browser-friendly and more useful to our users. We record information on Website traffic, but not on individual visitors to the Website, so no Personal Information about you will be kept or used. We will not merge personally-identifiable information with non-personally identifiable information previously collected from Display Advertising features that is based on the DoubleClick Web beacon.

## Visa Premium Cardholder Rate

The Visa Premium Cardholder Rate is an exclusive rate only available to eligible Visa Signature, Visa Infinite and Visa Platinum credit and debit cards. Kiwi Collection must confirm that all card numbers supplied for the Visa Premium Cardholder Rate are eligible for this exclusive rate. Accordingly, the credit or debit card number provided in connection with a Visa Premium Cardholder Rate booking will be transmitted to Visa Inc. to perform an online check for purposes of validating your card and eligibility.

## Disclaimer

Kiwi Collection Inc. endeavors to ensure that the Contents of this website are accurate and current. Nonetheless, despite our efforts this website may contain errors. Accordingly, Kiwi Collection Inc. disclaims any warranty of any kind, whether express of implied, regarding all information contained in and displayed on this website, including any use thereof, as well as any and all links to and from the website. 

Kiwi Collection Inc. does not warrant that the information included in our website is accurate, current, verified, comprehensive or complete. 

The information will, from time to time, be updated and/or changed, and Kiwi reserves the right to make all such changes to the content of this website without any obligation to advise and/or notify visitors to the website that such changes have been, or will be made. 

Currency conversion under license from openexchangerates.org ([End User Terms of Use](https://openexchangerates.org/terms)). 

If you have any questions or concerns feel free to email us.
